Guide to the Yale Play Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Yale play collection
1776-2010
RU 119
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.25
The collection consists of plays written by Yale students.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 47 (YRG 47), Collections documenting teaching and learning in Yale academic programs.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The materials are arranged chronologically.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of plays written by Yale students.
Plays (performed works); Yale College (1718-1887) -- Students; Yale University -- Students
- Yale student plays, 1776-2010; Accession 19ND-A-387
  - Andrus, Noah Y. (1777), Dialogue, 1776 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Gold, T.S., "The Reform", 1833 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Haskell, Daniel, "The Libertine", Circa 1802 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Schnee, Charles Y. (1936), TC of Doctor Dorothy, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - "The Student Body", 2009 April 23-25
    Scope and Contents
    The play was developed as an independent study project by Michael Leibenluft and written and developed by Andrew Chittenden, Kelsey Clark, Cory Finley, Peregrine Heard, Emily Hoffman, Cordelia Istel, Sophia Janowitz, Michael Leibenluft, Jacob Liberman, and Liz Mandeville in 2009. In 2010 the play was adapted to film.
    - Ephemera, 2009 April 23-25 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Videorecording of play, 2009; 1 (Box 2)
    - Movie version of play, 2010; 1 (Box 3)
  - Unidentified, Seven Plays, 1860s ? (Box 1, Folder 2)